Guide to the Howard Zinn Papers TAM.542
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Vietnam War, 1944-2001; 446829
  - Subseries VII:A: Vietnam War Material, 1944-2001; 446830
    - Post War: Remembering Vietnam, 1975, 1978-1979, undated; cuid16191; 446977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Post War: Repression in Vietnam, 1976-1977; cuid16192; 446984 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Post War: Southeast Asia, 1975-1978, undated; cuid16193; 446985 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Prisoners of War, 1971-1975; cuid16194; 446986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - "The Problem of Civil Liberties in South Vietnam" (student paper), undated; cuid16195; 446987 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Publications: Aggression from the North, 1965; cuid16196; 446988 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Publications: Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars, 1969-Summer 1972; cuid16197; 446989 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Publications: Bulletin of Concerned Asian Scholars, Dec 1972-1973; cuid16198; 446990 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Publications: Front Lines Soldiers' Writings from Vietnam (Indochina Curriculum Group), 1975; cuid16199; 446991 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Publications: Indochina Report, [1972]; cuid16200; 446992 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Publications: Peace in Vietnam: A New Approach to Southeast Asia (Quaker Working Party Paper), 1966; cuid16201; 446993 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Publications: Ramparts' Vietnam Primer, [1966]; cuid16202; 446994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Publications: The Second Front, 1968; cuid16203; 446995 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Publications: A Threat to Peace (U.S. State Department), 1961; cuid16204; 446996 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Publications: Three Documents of the National Liberation Front, 1970; cuid16205; 446997 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Publications: Various, 1970-1972; cuid16206; 446998 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Publications: Various, 1972-1973; cuid16207; 446999 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Publications: Various, 1973; cuid16208; 447000 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Publications: Viet Report, Oct 1965-Mar/Apr 1966; cuid16209; 447001 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Publications: Viet Report, Jun/Jul 1966-Jan/Feb 1967; cuid16210; 447002 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Publications: Why Vietnam (U.S. Government document defining America's role in Vietnam Conflict), 1965; cuid16211; 447003 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Rusk, Dean: Speech at Indiana University (Transcript), [1967]; cuid16212; 447025 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Saigon 1967 Elections, 1966-1967; cuid16213; 447026 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - The Secret Agent (film on Dioxin, Agent Orange and Vietnam Veterans): Controversy over Zinn Participation, 1983-1984; cuid16214; 447027 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Senate Hearings (notes), 1968; cuid16215; 447028 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Statements, 1967-1998, undated; cuid16216; 447029 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - "Telling it Like it Was: Vietnam History in the Schools" by William L. Griffen (article from Phi Delta Kappan), 1974; cuid16217; 447030 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Terror from the Sky, North Viet-Nam's Dikes and the U.S. Bombing by John Gliedman, 1972; cuid16218; 447031 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Text of President Nixon's Television Address, April 20, 1970, cuid16219; 447032 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - "Textbook Synthesis: Origins of U.S. Involvement", undated; cuid16220; 447033 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Tonkin Gulf, 1967-1971, undated; cuid16221; 447034 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Transparencies, undated; cuid16222; 447035 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Transparencies: Anti-War Protests, undated; cuid16223; 447036 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Transparencies: Automated Air War by National Action /Research on the Military Industrial Complex (NARMIC) (I), 1972; cuid16224; 447037 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Transparencies: Automated Air War by National Action /Research on the Military Industrial Complex (NARMIC) (II), 1972; cuid16225; 447038 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Transparencies: Automated Air War by National Action /Research on the Military Industrial Complex (NARMIC): Script and Footnotes, 1972; cuid16226; 447039 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Transparencies: Pro-War Demonstrations, undated; cuid16227; 447040 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Trials, 1971-1973, undated; cuid16228; 447041 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Opinion: "Of the People, By the People, For the People: Domestic Politics and the Interpretation of American Policy in Vietnam", 1974; cuid16229; 447042 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Policy: Statements, 1964-1966, undated; cuid16230; 447043 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - "Victory in Indochina", 1974-Apr 1975; cuid16231; 447044 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - "Victory in Indochina", May 1975; cuid16232; 447045 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - "Victory in Indochina", Jun 1975-Aug 1975; cuid16233; 447046 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - "Victory in Indochina", Sep 1975-1976; cuid16234; 447047 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Vietnam Documents (photocopies from Patrick J. Hurley Collection, University of Oklahoma Library), 1944-1945, 1966; cuid16235; 447048 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - The Vietnam Era, A Guide to Teaching Resources and other Indochina Curriculum Group Material, 1978, 1980; cuid16236; 447049 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Vietnam War, 1963-1964; cuid16237; 447050 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Vietnam War, 1965; cuid16238; 447051 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Vietnam War, 1966; cuid16239; 447052 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Vietnam War, 1967; cuid16240; 447053 (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Vietnam War, 1968; cuid16241; 447054 (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Vietnam War, 1969; cuid16242; 447055 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Vietnam War (clippings), 1969; cuid16243; 447056 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Vietnam War, 1970; cuid16244; 447057 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Vietnam War (clippings), 1970; cuid16245; 447058 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Vietnam War, 1971; cuid16246; 447059 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Vietnam War (clippings), 1971; cuid16247; 447060 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Vietnam War, 1972; cuid16248; 447061 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Vietnam War, 1973; cuid16249; 447062 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam War, 1974; cuid16250; 447063 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Vietnam War, 1975; cuid16251; 447064 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Vietnam War, undated; cuid16252; 447065 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - "Vietnamese Perspectives" by S.J. Noumoff, 1973; cuid16253; 447066 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Views of Other Countries, 1966, 1968, undated; cuid16254; 447067 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Violence (I), 1965-1972, undated; cuid16255; 447068 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Violence (II), 1965-1972, undated; cuid16256; 447069 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Violence (III), 1965-1972, undated; cuid16257; 447070 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - War Resistance, 1964-1969; cuid16258; 447071 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - War Resistance, 1970-1973, undated; cuid16259; 447072 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - War Resistance: Hawaii, 1968-1969, 1972; cuid16260; 447073 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Winter Soldier, 1971-1972, 1990, undated; cuid16261; 447074 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Zinn Articles, 1966-1972, 1985, undated; cuid16262; 447075 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Zinn Drafts and Notes, 1969, undated; cuid16263; 447076 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Zinn Drafts and Notes, undated; cuid16264; 447077 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Zinn Drafts and Notes: "Thinking about Vietnam, Political Theory and Human Life", undated; cuid16265; 447078 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: August (1966) Conferences, cuid16266; 447079 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: August (1966) Conferences - Correspondence, cuid16267; 447080 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: August (1966) Conferences - Zengakuren (All-Japan Federation of Student Autonomous Associations), 1964-1966; cuid16268; 447081 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: Business Cards, 1966; cuid16269; 447082 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: June (1966) Lecture Tour, 1965-1966, undated; cuid16270; 447083 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: Notebooks, 1966; cuid16271; 447084 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: Related Materials, 1964-1987, undated; cuid16272; 447085 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: Related Materials - Edwin O. Reischauer, 1966, undated; cuid16273; 447086 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Zinn Japan Trips: Talk Notes, [1966]; cuid16274; 447087 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Zinn Paris Trip 1968, cuid16275; 447088 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Zinn Speeches (includes drafts and a review), 1966, 1968, undated; cuid16276; 447089 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release, 1967-1968; cuid16277; 447090 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Clippings, 1967 - Feb 17, 1968; cuid16278; 447091 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Clippings, Feb 18, 1968 - Mar 13, 1968; cuid16279; 447092 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Correspondence, 1967-1970; cuid16280; 447093 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1968 Hanoi - Prisoner Release - Photographs, cuid16281; 447094 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: 1972, 1972-1973; cuid16282; 447095 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: Notebooks, [1968]; cuid16283; 447096 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Zinn Vietnam Trips: Notebooks, [1972]; cuid16284; 447097 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Subseries VII:B: The Pentagon Papers, 1971-1976; 446831
    - Clippings, 1971-1972, 1976, undated; cuid16285; 447128 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Clippings: Supreme Court Upholds Publication, 1971; cuid16286; 447129 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Clippings: Trial of Anthony J. Russo, Jr. and Daniel Ellsberg, 1973; cuid16287; 447130 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Clippings, Zinn Notes and Related Materials (includes copy of Zinn subpoena), 1971-1975, undated; cuid16288; 447131 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Court Documents: USA v. The New York Times, et al. - Amicus Curiae Brief, 1971; cuid16289; 447132 (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg, 1971-1973; cuid16290; 447133 (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit I Volume I "Vietnam and the US 1940-1950" (I), [1973]; cuid16291; 447134 (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit I Volume I "Vietnam and the US 1940-1950" (II), [1973]; cuid16292; 447135 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit II Volume II "US Involvement in the Franco-Viet Minh War", [1973]; cuid16293; 447136 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit III Volume IV A.2 "Aid for France in Indochina", [1973]; cuid16294; 447137 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit IV Volume IV A.3 "US and France's Withdrawal from Vietnam 1954-1956", [1973]; cuid16295; 447138 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit 9 Volume IV B.5 "The Overthrow of Ngo Dinh Diem, May-Nov, 1963" (I), [1973]; cuid16296; 447139 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Exhibit 9 Volume IV B.5 "The Overthrow of Ngo Dinh Diem, May-Nov, 1963" (II), [1973]; cuid16297; 447140 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Court Documents: USA v. Anthony J. Russo, Jr., Daniel Ellsberg - Zinn Testimony (includes notes and clippings), 1973; cuid16298; 447141 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - "Daniel Ellsberg and the Power of the Peacemakers" by Stewart Burns (draft and letter to Zinn), 1977; cuid16299; 447142 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - House Committee on Government Operations: FOIA Reports, 1972, 1973; cuid16300; 447143 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Availability of Information to Congress, Apr 1973; cuid16301; 447144 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Part 4 and Part 5, Mar 6, 1972-Mar 28, 1972; cuid16302; 447145 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Part 6 and Part 7, Apr 11, 1972-May 11, 1972; cuid16303; 447146 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - The Pentagon Papers (Part 1 and Part 2), Jun 23, 1971-Jun 29, 1971; cuid16304; 447147 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - The Pentagon Papers (Part 3), Jun 30 and Jul 7, 1971; cuid16305; 447148 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - House Government Operations Subcommittee: Hearings - Problems of Congress in Obtaining Information from the Executive Branch (Part 8), May 12, 1972-Jun 1, 1972; cuid16306; 447149 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Notes, undated; cuid16307; 447151 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - A Pentagon Papers Digest, Indochina Information Project, undated; cuid16308; 447152 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Publication Announcement, 1971; cuid16309; 447153 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume I (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16310; 447155 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume II (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16311; 447157 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume III (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16312; 447158 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume IV (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), [1971]; cuid16313; 447159 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume V (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), 1972; cuid16314; 447161 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - The Pentagon Papers, Gravel Edition: Volume V - Review, 1974; cuid16315; 447163 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - The Pentagon Papers, The New York Times Series (Zinn copy with notes and annotations), 1971; cuid16316; 447164 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Russo, Anthony, 1973, 1995, undated; cuid16317; 447205 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - "Servants of the State": Studs Terkel Interview with Daniel Ellsberg, Anthony Russo and Eqbal Ahmad, 1972; cuid16318; 447208 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Series VIII: Subject Files, 1933-2010; 447315
  This series contains materials on a wide range of topics, representing either research for books, articles and lectures or merely items clipped and saved based on Zinn's many personal interests. Some of the largest subject areas are the Gulf Wars, Central America, the Central Intelligence Agency, civil liberties, crime and punishment, East Asia (especially China), prisons, terrorism and trials (including many at which Zinn provided testimony). There are many folders which Zinn labeled either "Hope" or "Resistance"; they contain collected articles, clippings, flyers, notes and individual documents describing various events or acts of resistance which appeared to him to be reasons for hope and optimism.
  Some of the materials in this series, particularly newspaper clippings, are in poor condition. Also, because Zinn's method of clipping articles sometimes meant merely saving the portion of interest to him, many pieces are incomplete and may lack publication title and/or date.
  - Abortion (Zinn notes), undated; cuid16319; 447318 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Academic Contacts, 1973-1975, undated; cuid16320; 447320 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia, 1985-1987, undated; cuid16321; 447322 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia - Reader, Mark, 1985; cuid16322; 447323 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Academic Freedom: Accuracy in Academia - Zinn Appearance on Today Show (correspondence), 1985; cuid16323; 447324 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Action, 1971-1974, undated; cuid16324; 447325 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Action Strategies, 1963-1969; cuid16325; 447327 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Action Strategies, 1970-1979, undated; cuid16326; 447328 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Africa, 1960-1965; cuid16327; 447335 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Africa, 1967, undated; cuid16328; 447336 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Africa: Zimbabwe: A New History, 1982; cuid16329; 447337 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Agnew, Spiro T.: Conviction and Sentence, 1973; cuid16330; 447338 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - American Civil Liberties Union, Massachusetts (CLUM): Zinn Notes in Preparation for Speech, undated; cuid16331; 447340 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - American Historical Association (AHA) and the Radical Historians Caucus, 1969-Mar 1970; cuid16332; 447342 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - American Historical Association (AHA) and the Radical Historians Caucus, Apr 1970-1976, undated; cuid16333; 447344 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Anarchism, 1968-1982, undated; cuid16334; 447346 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Anarchism: American Anarchism, 1971-1981, undated; cuid16335; 447347 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Anarchism: Bibliography, 1969-1975; cuid16336; 447349 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Anarchism: "Introduction I", 1968-1977, undated; cuid16337; 447351 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Anarchism: Spanish Anarchists (Spanish Civil War), 1986-1988; cuid16338; 447352 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Anti-Communism, 1950-1959; cuid16339; 447354 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Anti-Communism, 1983-2002, undated; cuid16340; 447356 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Communism: House Un-American Activities Committee (HUAC), 1963, undated; cuid16341; 447357 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Communism: Informers, 1955-1956, 1961; cuid16342; 447358 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Art and Politics, 1968-1989; cuid16343; 447359 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Art and Politics, 1990-2005; cuid16344; 447360 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Art and Politics, undated; cuid16345; 447361 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Art and Politics: Artists, 2001-2007, undated; cuid16346; 447362 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Art and Politics: Artists and War, 1995-2008, undated; cuid16347; 447363 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Art and Politics: Literature, 1953, 1963-1981; cuid16348; 447364 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Art and Politics: Literature (notes, summaries, excerpts of books, films, poetry), undated; cuid16349; 447365 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Art and Politics: Protest Literature, 1988-2005, undated; cuid16350; 447366 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Art and Politics: War and Art, 2002-2007, undated; cuid16351; 447367 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Bakunin, Michael, 1976, 1985, undated; cuid16352; 447368 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Barrett, James W., 1972-1975, undated; cuid16353; 447370 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Barrett, James W.: Court Documents, 1974, 1995-1996; cuid16354; 447371 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Berrigan, Daniel and Philip Berrigan, 1970-1978, 2002, 2003, undated; cuid16355; 447372 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Berrigan, Daniel and Philip Berrigan: Danbury Photograph of Daniel, undated; cuid16356; 447373 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Buckley, Jr., William F.: Articles and Notes, 1970-1971, undated; cuid16357; 447374 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Buber, Martin: Excerpt from The Letters of Martin Buber: A Life of Dialogue, 1996; cuid16358; 449260 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 1999-2005, undated; cuid16359; 447376 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 2000-2005; cuid16360; 447377 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Bush, George W. Administration, 2007, undated; cuid16361; 447378 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Bush, George W. Administration: Foreign Policy, May 2001-Dec 2001; cuid16362; 447379 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Bush, George W. Administration: Impeachment, 2006, undated; cuid16363; 447380 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Calendars (commemorative): Julius C.C. Edelstein and Women's Leadership (in Spanish), 2003, 2006; cuid16364; 447381 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Carter, Jimmy, 1976-1979, undated; cuid16365; 447382 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Carter, Jimmy: "'76 Politics", 1975-1978, undated; cuid16366; 447383 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights (CCR): Fall 1999 Docket, cuid16367; 447385 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair), 1987-2001, undated; cuid16368; 447387 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): "Contragate and Foreign Policy Overview", 1984-1994, undated; cuid16369; 447389 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): "Deception Law and Contragate", 1984-1991, undated; cuid16370; 447392 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): Hasenfus, Eugene, 1985-1987; cuid16371; 447393 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Central America: Contragate (Iran Contra Affair): Iran-Reagan Crisis, 1986-1987, undated; cuid16372; 447395 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Central America: History, 1990-1992, undated; cuid16373; 447396 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Central America: History (clippings), 1984-2009, undated; cuid16374; 447397 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Central America: Law, 1981-1985, undated; cuid16375; 447399 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Central America: In Contempt of Congress, The Reagan Record of Deceit and Illegality on Central America, 1985; cuid16376; 447402 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Central America: Nicaragua, 1983-1988, undated; cuid16377; 447404 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Central America: Panama (includes letter from John Kerry), 1989-1991, 2003, undated; cuid16378; 447458 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (CIA), 1973-1985, undated; cuid16379; 447459 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: "Bizarre Activities and Lies", 1976, 1978, 1983, undated; cuid16380; 447460 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: The CIA and the Cult of Intelligence by Marchetti and Marks (with several news clippings), 1974, [1977], 1978; cuid16381; 447461 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volumes 1 and 2, Sep 1975; cuid16382; 447462 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volumes 2 and 4, Sep 1975-Oct 1975; cuid16383; 447463 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Hearings Volume 6, Nov 1975; cuid16384; 447464 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Interim Report "Alleged Assassination Plots Involving Foreign Leaders", Nov 1975; cuid16385; 447465 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book I "Foreign and Military Intelligence, Apr 1976; cuid16386; 447466 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book III "Supplementary Detailed Staff Reports on Intelligence Activities and the Rights of Americans", Apr 1976; cuid16387; 447467 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book IV "Supplementary Detailed Staff Reports on Foreign and Military Intelligence", Apr 1976; cuid16388; 447468 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Investigations - Church Committee (Senate Select Committee to Study Government Operations with Respect to Intelligence Activities) Report - Book VI "Supplementary Reports on Intelligence Activities", Apr 1976; cuid16389; 447469 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Iran Contra - Breeden, BIll, 1986-1990, 1992, undated; cuid16390; 447471 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Central Intelligence Agency: Iran Contra - Bush, George, 1986, 1989, undated; cuid16391; 447472 (Box 42, Folder 14)